question_data = [{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "The 2010 film &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "Han Solo&#039;s co-pilot and best friend, &quot;Chewbacca&quot;, is an Ewok.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio&#039;s character hunts down the killer of his son.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "The film &quot;2001: A Space Odyssey&quot; was released on December 31st, 2000.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherf*cker&#039; in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]
}]